Looking for a place where I can go
These got their hive, moles got their hole
Looking for a place for me to go
My paws are aching because I've been walking
I've seen one million trees
Well trees belong in the forest
But where's the place for me?
Ow, huh?
I said ow.
It got you guys!
Thanks for catching us.
We totally would have died.
I really died.
Here's nothing.
Ow.
I'm grisby the way.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Panda.
I can't believe it survived that.
You were amazing, man.
The way you came in, like, whoosh, bam!
And you were like, pow!
And then, like, just, just, just, just, oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
And I was like, and I was like, uh, uh, uh.
Hey, I was not like that.
Wow, we'll make a great game.
Wait a second.
Something... something's coming to me.
Hold on.
I don't think...
Okay, I just got a crazy idea.
What if we kept this team thing going?
What do you mean?
You know, like, we stick together.
Have each other's backs.
And take care of each other.
Like, a family?
Yeah, exactly.
And now, make us brothers.
But we don't even look alike.
I know!
That's like, the best part.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess it is.
Cool.
I know how brothers.
Yes!
What's the problem with the three of us are brothers.
My life!
No matter what happens, we'll always be there for each other.
Yeah, and to put each other.
All right.
Roach for life on three.
One, two, three.
Roach for life.
Ah!
Woo-hoo!
Pick me!
I'm a good one.
You're looking out for your life.
I'm cute too.
I'm a high-ball, all our jammin'.
Pick me!
Oh, here!
I'm a pain!
Oh.
Dang it.
Lost another one.
I just don't get it.
I thought it was coming to this adoption store and help us find a home for sure.
Huh?
All right, guys.
Time to call the night.
Good time, staff.
Just like we practice.
Okay, bro.
Let's suit up.
All we're gonna do is wait.
That's strange for the last ones.
What?
Woo-hoo!
There he is!
Ah!
You ran up, folks.
Step right up.
Come see the adorable bears for sale.
Just 25 cents.
For free even.
Whatever fits in your budget.
All right, bro.
Time to step up our game.
Do a cute pose, PanPan.
Pee!
A durable.
Now you little bro.
Oh, so adorable.
I'll make you a deal.
You can stay if you help bringing customers.
Well, just until someone wins us, right?
I'm trying to get a doctor.
I'm gonna do it.
I know someone wins us, right?
I'm trying to get a doctor.
Huh?
Adopted.
Oh, yeah, sure, right.
Ok, Lewis.
You got a mic?
And some fresh beats?
You know, let's show these nice people what real fun looks like.
Flann!
Busset,我是 Brian Busset.
Christopher Busset.
Kickin' Pan.
Kickin' Pan!
Go Little Bro!
GoLittle Bro, GoLittle Bro Go!
Go Little Bro, GoLittle Bro, GoLittle Bro, Go!
Pow!
Ah!
Huh!
Lewis?
What is this below me?
This is rigged!
Come on, bro.
Let's go elsewhere.
There you go.
Now let's blow this bottle stand.
You can find Lewis.
You've brought him to fire!
Oh, hey, little friend.
You must be homeless too.
You went in on our dreams?
Hey.
Oh.
Huh?
Guys, wake up.
You got to see this.
Oh.
Where are we?
Nice morning.
Yeah.
I slept really well.
And this place isn't so bad.
Iceberg not entirely opposed.
Yeah, this place is great.
New window.
Iceberg has made front door.
Boos!